"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
你还记得你初来这里
You remember that bamboo field you woke up in
醒来时所在的那个竹林吗? 穿过那片竹林 再跨过一座桥
when you first got here? Beyond that field, across a ridge,
就是岛的心脏地带了 光就在那儿
is the heart of the island. That's where the light is.
那儿也是他的目的地
That's where he's trying to go,
- 所以你必须去保护它  - 我得保护多久?
- And that's what you have to protect.  - How long am I gonna have to do this job?
直到生命的终点 喝了这个 你就跟我一样了
As long as you can. Drink this. Now you're like me.
- Desmond Hume就是被我扔进这口井里去的  - 啊!
- This is the well I threw Desmond Hume into.  - Aah!
- 貌似有人帮他逃了出来  - 不 Ben 是有人帮忙把我弄了出来
- Looks like someone helped him out.  - No, Ben, someone helped me out.
我要找到Desmond
I'm gonna find Desmond.
等我找到他后 我就毁了这个岛
And when I do, I'm gonna destroy the island.
前几天有一场交通肇事逃逸事故
There was a hit-and-run a few days ago
地点是华盛顿Tustin中学
at Washington Tustin high school.
- 然后?  - 我就是嫌犯
- Yeah?  - I'm the suspect.
下午好 你今天过得如何?
Good afternoon. And how are you doing today?
再好不过了
Terrific.
是时候走人了
I think it's time to leave.
你跟着他 你跟着我
You're with him, and you're with me.
我们去听音乐会
We are going to a concert.
走吧
Let's go.
大洋航空
遗体
- 需要人签收么?  - 你是这里的员工?
- Do you need somebody to sign for that?  - You work here?
如假包换 伙计
I do indeed, brother.
你是牧师 还是其他啥的?
You a priest or somethin'?
我不是牧师
Or something.
介意把东西运到那后面去么?
Do you mind taking it around the back there?
没问题 我这就运过去
Yeah, sure. You got it.
运到那边就好 谢谢
Just around there. Thank you.
谁去世了?
Who died?
一个名叫Christian Shephard的男子
A man named Christian Shephard.
"Christian Shephard"吗?
"Christian Shephard"?
真的?
Seriously?
真的
Seriously.
你朋友?
Friend of yours?
不算吧
Not exactly.
等... 等会儿
H... hang on a second.
你带我越狱 让我穿上这件礼服
You bust me out of jail and make me put on this dress
说咱俩要去啥音乐会
so that we can go to some concert,
可你竟连我们来这儿的原因 都不告诉我?
and you won't even tell me why we're here?
没人能告诉你到这儿来的理由 Kate
No one can tell you why you're here, Kate.
- 总之我没办法告诉你  - 是你带我来的啊
- Certainly not me.  - You're the one who brought me here.
我说的不是教堂
I'm not talking about the church.
我是说尘世
I'm talking about here.
你是谁?
Who are you?
你想干嘛?
What do you want?
我叫Desmond Hume
My name is Desmond Hume.
甚至你可能都没意识到 我是你的朋友
And even though you don't realize it, I'm your friend.
至于我想干嘛...
And as for what I want...
我不过是想离开
I want to leave.
离开去哪儿?
Leave and go where?
我带你去看
Let me show you.
你没事吧?
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
你呢?
You?
说实话 医生 我想知道
Well, to be honest, doc, I'm kinda wondering
刚刚到底发生了什么事
what the hell just happened up here.
我也想知道呢
That makes two of us.
那你现在是新任Jacob 对么?
So you're the new Jacob, huh?
感觉有啥不同?
Feel any different?
没啥感觉
Not really.
医生 不如你下山
Well, doc, how about you come down off the mountaintop
告诉我们 林子失火
and tell us what the hell the burning bush
意味着什么?
had to say for itself?
Jacob告诉我 我们得去旧营地的
Jacob told me that we have to go to the bamboo forest
竹林
out past our old camp.
穿过竹林
Just past it, well,
他说 我们就可以找到要保护的地方
he said I'd find the place that we need to protect.
那里... 到底是个什么样的地方?
This place... what is it?
他说 它是岛的心脏
He called it the heart of the island.
他说 所谓的心脏...
All he said was that it's...
就是光
it's a light.
而且扮成Locke的烟怪想要扑灭它?
And that Locke smoke thing wants to put it out?
嗯 差不多吧
Something like that, yeah.
如果他把光灭了呢?
So what if he does?
那我们就玩完了
Then that's it for all of us.
但... 如果Locke意在扑灭它 他为啥不去灭?
But... but if Locke wants to put it out, then why hasn't he?
因为他还缺点儿什么
'Cause he ain't got what he needs.
我猜 他缺的是Desmond
I'm guessing that'd be Desmond.
所以在你就职之前 这就是我们的目标
That's where we were headed before your inauguration.
Sayid说过 Locke把他扔进了一口井
Sayid said Locke tossed him in a well.
Jacob没跟我说过任何关于Desmond的事
Jacob didn't say anything to me about Desmond.
他似乎什么也没说过啊
Doesn't sound like he said anything about anything.
这倒是真的 他表现得真不像个智者
That's kinda true, dude. He's worse than Yoda.
好吧 你们都去岛的心脏地带
All right, y'all head to your heart of the island,
我去抓逃出井的小妖
and I'll go get the magic leprechaun out of that well.
如果我们留下路标 你追得上来么?
If we leave a trail, can you catch up with us?
- 嗯 没问题  - 注意安全
- Hell, yeah, I can.  - Then be safe.
我本想叫你一起去的 不过如果又告诉你
I'd ask you along, but that'd take all the fun
- 你不能去 那才叫扫兴  - 呃 我看
- out of me telling you you can't come.  - Uh, I guess
我得拼命克制跟你同去的念头了
I'll just have to resist the urge to follow you anyway.
我有种不祥的预感
I got a bad feeling about this.
迷失 第6季第17-18集
我不知道你干嘛带我越狱
I don't know why you got me out of prison,
也不知道你的目的和身份
what you want or who you are,
但你应该知道 我担不起责任...
but you understand I can't be held responsible for...
嗯 嗯 我都明白 兄弟
Yeah, yeah, whatever, dude.
看见这东西 能想起来啥不?
None of this is ringing a bell, is it?
你 我... 麻醉枪?
You, me... tranquilizer gun?
你神经病啊
You are insane.
好吧 我神经病 你好生在这儿待着
Okay. Fine. I'm insane. Just wait here.
要是我不呢?
What if I don't?
随你的便
Then that's your choice.
但如果你选择继续跟着我...
But if you stick with me...
有朝一日 你会无比庆幸
you'll be happy you did.
来了 来了 来了
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我明明挂了"请勿打扰"的标志
"Do no disturb" sign.
你是谁?
Who are you?
你干嘛笑得像个傻子?
Why you grinnin' like a sodding idiot?
呃 你今晚有场音乐会要出演
Uh, you have a concert to perform tonight,
我是来接你的
and I'm here to pick you up.
我对Widmore的另一个白痴 说得不够清楚么?
Didn't I make it clear to Widmore's other monkey?
我才不在乎什么破音乐会
I don't care about a sodding concert.
Charlie啊...
Charlie...
Charlie 如果我告诉你...
Charlie, what if I told you that...
出演这场音乐会
playing this show is
将是你人生中最重要的一件事呢?
the most important thing you'll ever do?
你会去么?
Would you come then?
滚
Sod off.
好吧 兄弟 抱歉了
Okay, dude. Sorry about this.
那是啥?
What was that?
Charlie呗
That was Charlie.
你为什么要接手这工作 Jack?
Why did you take the job, Jack?
因为我应该接手
Because I was supposed to.
为什么? 就因为有个陌生人 把我们的名字写在了墙上?
Why? Because some stranger wrote our names on a wall?
我会接手 是因为这个岛是我的唯一
I took it because the island's all I've got left.
它是我这一生 唯一一个我不想毁掉的东西
It's the only thing in my life I haven't managed to ruin.
你什么都没毁啊
You haven't ruined anything.
没有什么是不可挽回的
Nothing is irreversible.
如果我们不是都得死的话 这话听着还真叫人舒心
This would be so sweet if we weren't all about to die.
既然你都在旁看着了 那干嘛不一起玩玩?
As long as you're watching, why don't you join us?
你到这儿来干嘛 James?
What are you doing here, James?
我听说Desmond落井了
I heard Desmond fell in the well,
所以我来帮忙拉他出来
so I came to help him get out.
看来有人已经抢先我们一步 把他救走了
Looks like somebody beat us both to the punch.
哦 真好
Oh, well.
你知道我干嘛到这儿来吗?
Do you know why I'm here?
我猜 你是因为需要Desmond来毁了这个岛
I'm guessing you need Desmond to destroy the island.
答得真准
That's absolutely right.
然后呢 烟怪? 和船一起沉了?
Then what, Smokey? You going down with the ship?
自杀貌似不符合你的风格
Suicide doesn't seem like your style.
我不会死的
I'm not going down with anything.
但你和剩下的那些Jacob的小"候选人"
But you and the rest of Jacob's little "candidates"
绝对会死
absolutely are.
我们不再是候选人了
We're not candidates anymore.
哦! 哦!
Ohh! Oh!
啊
Aah.
再见啦
I'll be seein' ya.
你不去追他?
You're not gonna go after him?
不需要
I don't need to.
当你说 你要毁了这个岛的时候
When you said you were gonna destroy the island,
我还以为你是在打比方
I thought you were speaking figuratively.
就因为我曾经说过 等我走了 一切由你接管?
Because I said I'd leave you in charge once I was gone?
如果我弄沉了这个岛
I'm sorry if I left out the part
那我得说声抱歉
about the island being on the bottom of the ocean.
换句话说 欢迎你和我一起坐船走
That being said, you're welcome to join me on my boat.
因为我们一旦驱使Desmond 做了我们要他做的事
Because once we get Desmond to do what we need him to do,
我就坐船离开这个蛮荒之地
I'm gonna sail away from this godforsaken place
还要亲眼看着它沉没
and watch it sink.
之前有条狗来过这儿
I think there was a dog here.
早上好
Morning.
睡得好么?
Sleep okay?
嗯
Aye.
你的帐篷比井底舒服多了
Your camp's a lot nicer than the bottom of a well.
我想我该把这当成是一种赞美
I think I'm gonna go ahead and take that as a compliment.
你是要继续对着他喋喋不休
Are you gonna talk his ear off,
还是去给他拿点儿早餐?
or you gonna get the man some breakfast?
我去看看捕鱼机
Guess I'll go check the traps for fish.
走吧 Vincent
Come on. Vincent.
我们走
Let's go.
呃 Rose 跟我说说...
So, Rose, tell me...
你俩在这儿住了多久?
how long have the two of you been living here?
我们75年盖的房子
Well, we built this place in '75,
然后... 住了几年
and... lived here a couple of years,
再然后 一切好转了
and then the sky lit up again.
现在只有上帝知道 我们何时进地狱了
So God only knows when in the hell we are now.
所以... Desmond...
So... Desmond...
我无心冒犯
I don't mean to be rude,
但等你用餐完毕 我想请你离开
but after you eat, I'm gonna ask you to move on.
我们为你破了例
We broke our rule with you.
破了什么例
What rule is that?
我们不会参与其中
We don't get involved.
不管是什么东西把你丢进井里的...
Whatever got you tossed inside a well...
那都是我和Bernard
That's the kind of drama
不愿的浑水
Bernard and I don't want to have anything to do with.
这没错
Fair enough.
看来你捕到鱼了
Looks like you caught something.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你好 Rose
Hello, Rose.
直奔主题吧
I'll make this simple.
要么你现在跟我走
Come with me now
要么我就当着你的面 杀了他们
or I'll kill them both right in front of you.
你哪里都不用跟他去
You don't have to go anywhere with him.
我会让他们受尽痛苦
I'll make it hurt.
我要你保证
I want your word.
不动他们
You won't touch them.
- 永远不动  - 一言为定
- Ever.  - Done.
那我悉听尊便
Then I'll do what you want.
好 Desmond
Yes, Desmond.
听话就好
You will.
Desmond 你知道我要带你去哪儿吗?
You have any idea where I'm taking you, Desmond?
不知道
No.
但我猜你要带我去个非常亮堂的地方
But I assume it's a place where there's a very bright light.
何以见得?
What makes you say that?
哦... 直觉
Oh... just a hunch.
- 什么响?  - 什么?
- What was that?  - What was what?
Linus 能听见我吗? 快回话
Linus, can you hear me? Come in.
我找到了Alpert
I found Alpert.
Linus啊
Linus?
该死
Damn it.
你没事吧?
You okay?
怎... 怎... 怎么了?
What... what... what happened?
你以为跟
You thought it'd be a good idea
黑烟谈谈行得通
to talk to the black smoke.
可结果它把你扔进了该死的丛林
It responded by throwing you into the damn jungle.
Locke 啊...
Locke. L...
- 他在吗?  - 不在
- Is he still here?  - No.
来
Here.
我想用对讲机联系Linus
I've been trying to get Linus on the walkie.
可他一直没接
He won't pick up.
- 来 我们找人帮帮忙  - 帮忙? 帮忙? 找谁?
- Come on. Let's get you some help.  - Help? Help? Help from where?
炸弹没丢吧? 我是说... C4炸弹?
You still have the explosives? The... the C-4?
没丢 怎么了?
Yeah. Why?
我们要去另一个岛
Because we need to go to the other island
将我们所做的一切来个了结 炸了那架飞机
and finish what we started. We need to blow up that plane.
- Ford探员  - Jim 是我
- Detective Ford.  - Jim, it's me.
- 我想我刚看见了那个叫Jarrah的家伙  - 你在区监狱?
- I think I just saw that Jarrah guy.  - You at County Lockup?
不是 我在我父亲的博物馆义演音乐会
No, I'm at my dad's museum concert benefit thing.
那不可能是Jarrah
Well, it can't be Jarrah.
- 一小时前 我刚把他送上去区监狱的车  - 你确定?
- I just put him in a van to county an hour ago.  - Really?
- 我刚打过电话 他们说车根本没到  - 什么?
- Because I just called, and they said it never showed up.  - What?
Jim 帮帮我
Help me out here, Jim.
Jarrah冷血地枪击了四个人
Jarrah popped four people in cold blood.
只有一名受害者生还 没错吧?
Only one witness left the scene alive, right?
- 貌似是个韩国女人 你能保证她的安全吗?  - 对 没错 Sun Paik
- Some Korean woman. Can you make sure she's okay?  - Yeah, yeah. Sun Paik.
受了枪伤 还在医院
Gunshot wound. She's still over at the hospital.
Enos 好好欣赏音乐会吧 我会保护她
Enjoy your concert, Enos. I'll keep her safe.
感觉怎么样
有点儿疼
中枪了当然会疼
医生会来给宝宝做检查
如果一切都好的话
他们说我们马上就可以出院
离开?
然后一直躲着我父亲?
我打扰到你们了吗?
Am I interrupting?
嗨 Paik夫人 我是Juliet Carlson
Hi. Ms. Paik, I'm Juliet Carlson.
我是来给你的宝宝做检查的
I'm here to make sure your baby's okay.
你是孩子父亲吧
You must be the daddy.
抱歉 你们不会说英语
I'm sorry. You don't speak English.
我... 我尽量少说话
I'm.... I'll try not to talk too much.
好的 把外衣卷起一点儿
Okay, you lift up your gown a little bit.
会有些凉
It's a little cold.
好了 我们看看
Okay. Let's take a look.
没事吧?
Okay?
你没事吧?
我...
想起来了
想起什么了?
在这儿
There it is.
你们的孩子
There's your baby.
你看见了吗?
看见那个小小的摆动吗?
Do you see that little flutter?
那儿?
Right there?
那是宝宝的心跳
That's the baby's heartbeat.
一切非常正常
Perfectly perfect in every way.
羊水诊断有结果了 各项都检查好了
I have your amnio results. Everything checked out.
想知道是男孩儿 还是女孩儿吗?
Would you like to know if it's a boy or a girl?
是女孩儿
It's a girl.
没错
Yeah.
她叫Jin Yeon
Her name is Jin Yeon.
好可爱的名字
That's a lovely name.
顺便提一下 你们俩英文说得不赖
And for the record, y... you two speak English just fine.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
哇哦! 大脚 别紧张 是我
Whoa! Easy, Bigfoot. It's just me.
我找到Locke了
I found Locke.
那混蛋说要毁了这个岛
Son of a bitch said he's gonna destroy the island.
你说得没错 医生
You had it right, doc.
好消息是 Desmond逃出了那口井
Good news is, Desmond got out of that well,
- 所以 如果我们可以在黑烟之前找到他...  - James 谁找到Desmond都无所谓了
- so if we can find him before Smokey can...  - It doesn't matter if we find Desmond or he does, James.
反正都是殊途同归
We're all going to the same place anyway.
然后呢?
Then what?
画上一个句点
Then it ends.
- 你好 Locke先生  - Shephard医生
- Hello, Mr. Locke.  - Dr. Shephard.
嘿 既然你都要切开我的背
Hey, since you're about to open up my back,
不如先叫我John吧
you can probably start calling me John.
好吧 John
Okay, John.
我想先过来打个招呼
I thought I'd stop by and say hi
然后再开始麻醉
before we started the anesthesia.
紧张吗?
You nervous?
你确定这能行?
Are you sure this is gonna work?
没错
Yes.
我保证会成功的
I'm very confident that it will.
真的吗?
Really?
总会有机会杀了你的...
Well, there's always the chance that I could kill you...
不过我想让你好受点
but I'm trying to make you feel better.
好吧 好吧 那开始吧
Okay. Okay, let's do it.
嗯 我在那边等你
All right. I'll see you on the other side.
嘿 医生 之前在洛杉矶机场 在行李认领处的时候
Hey, doctor, back at L.A.X., when we met at baggage claim,
你说你父亲失踪了
you mentioned that they had lost your father.
- 后来有找到吗?  - 其实 今早我接到电话
- Did he ever turn up?  - As a matter of fact, I got a phone call this morning.
- 他们 呃 找到了棺材  - 哦 太好了
- They, uh, they found the coffin.  - Oh, good.
可能现在就已经运来了
Actually, it might be here already.
那么 希望这能让你安心
Well, I hope that brings you some peace.
Locke先生 如果我可以医好你
If I can fix you, Mr. Locke,
就足够安心了
that's all the peace I'll need.
大风大浪即将来临
It's gonna be a hell of a storm.
欢迎加入
Welcome to the club.
什么?
What?
你不介意吧?
You mind?
看来你长了第一根白头发
Looks like you got your first gray hair.
你笑什么?
What are you smiling about?
我刚意识到我渴望生存
I think I just realized that I want to live.
真是时候
It's good timing.
那是什么?
What was that?
救命!
Help!
嘿!
Hey!
嘿! Miles 前面!
Hey! Miles, up ahead!
嘿!
Hey!
哦
Ohh.
给他点儿水
Get him some water.
你们来这儿干嘛?
What are you guys doing out here?
我们要去九头蛇岛把飞机炸了
We're going to Hydra Island to blow up a plane.
为什么?
What do you want to do that for?
因为黑烟意图逃出岛
Because the black smoke wants to get off the island,
我们必须阻止它
and we have to stop that thing from leaving.
如果我们离开了 那玩意儿就没飞机可用了
Well, if we leave, that thing won't have a plane anymore.
没错 可是要怎么做?
Yeah, and how are we gonna do that?
你们还不知道吧 我是个飞行员
In case you haven't noticed, I'm a pilot.
- 这下有趣儿了  - Kate!
- Well, this is gonna be interesting.  - Kate!
Kate啊
Kate!
是你杀了他们!
You killed them!
Kate! 够了
Kate! That's it.
- 够了  - 省省子弹吧
- That's it.  - You might wanna save your bullets.
是你
So it's you.
没错 是我
Yeah, it's me.
Jacob还是老样子
Jacob being who he is,
我还以为能有点儿小惊喜呢
I expected to be a little more surprised.
选你 那不是明摆着的嘛
You're sort of the obvious choice,
- 你说呢?  - 他没有选我 是我自愿的
- don't you think?  - He didn't choose me. I volunteered.
我猜你是来阻止我的
I assume you're here to stop me.
我阻止不了你
I can't stop you.
事实上 我 呃 想跟你一起走
In fact, I, uh, I wanna go with you.
抱歉 Jack
I'm sorry, Jack.
我想你有点儿搞不清楚状况
I think you're a little confused about what I came here to do.
没有
No, I'm not.
你要去竹林的另一头...
No, you're going to the far side of the bamboo forest...
那个我誓死要保护的地方
to the place that I've sworn that I'll protect.
- 你还认为你要毁了这座岛  - 我"认为"?
- And then you think you're gonna destroy the island.  - I "think"?
没错 因为这事不会发生
That's right, because that's not what's gonna happen.
Jack 那什么会发生?
Then what's gonna happen, Jack?
我会干掉你
I'm gonna kill you.
你打算怎么做?
How do you plan to do that?
会给你个惊喜
It's a surprise.
好吧
Okay.
那么走着瞧
Then let's get on with it.
医生
Doctor.
没想到你今天还上班啊
I didn't know you were working today.
活儿还没干完呢 你拿到音乐会的票了吗?
I just finished. Did you get the tickets for the concert?
拿到了 在这儿
Yeah. Right here.
嘿 爸爸 还记得票的事吗?
Hey, dad, did you remember the tickets?
我刚给你妈了
I just gave them to your mom.
- 呃 谁拿你这张呢?  - 如果你找不到其他人的话
- Uh, who's gonna take yours?  - Well, if you don't have anybody else,
或许你可以带Claire阿姨一起去
maybe you could take aunt Claire.
- 我想她会喜欢去外面走走的  - 哦 没错 我没意见
- I'm sure she'd love to get out of the house.  - Oh, yeah. It's fine with me.
事实上 我对你这位神秘的妹妹非常好奇
In fact, I'm very curious to meet this mysterious sister
我们结婚那么久 你对她只字未提
you never mentioned the entire time we were married.
我保证你会喜欢她的 她快生了
Well, I'm sure you're gonna love her. She's extremely pregnant.
祝你手术成功 医生
Good luck on your surgery, doctor.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 挑好领带了吗?  - 挑好了
- Did you pick out a tie?  - I did.
很好
Nice.
嗨 我是洛杉矶警局的Ford探员
Hi. I'm Detective Ford, L.A.P.D.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
我要找一间病房... 叫Sun Paik的
I'm looking for a patient's room... Sun Paik.
你不想和大伙儿分享点什么故事吗 医生?
Something you wanna share with the rest of us, doc?
指什么?
What's that?
你说过你会杀死Locke的
You said you were gonna kill Locke.
- 你所谓的惊喜是什么?  - Desmond
- What's your surprise?  - Desmond.
那有什么用啊?
And how's that gonna work?
我也不知道 我不相信Jacob
I'm not sure yet. I can't believe Jacob
会总让他回到这个岛上
would've brought him all the way back to this island
好让Locke利用他毁了这个岛
just so Locke could make him destroy it.
- 那又怎么样? Desmond是个诱饵?  - 不
- So what? Desmond's bait?  - No.
我觉得他是件武器
I think he's a weapon.
越听越糊涂了 医生
That's a hell of a long con, doc.
Jack和Desmond...
Jack, Desmond...
这儿只要我们三个人就行了
It should just be the three of us from here on.
Jack啊
Jack.
我相信你 哥们
I believe in you, dude.
这竹子要垮了
It's gonna be a bad one.
我们到了
We're here.
这么做无济于事的
This doesn't matter, you know.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
他要毁了这个岛 你要灭了他...
Him destroying the island, you destroying him...
有什么用呢
It doesn't matter.
你们把我放下去找那束光
I mean, you're gonna lower me into that light,
我会去另一个地方...
and I'm gonna go somewhere else...
在那儿 我们可以和喜欢的人待在一起
a place where we can be with the ones that we love
不用再考虑这个该死的岛了
and not have to ever think about this damn island again.
你知道最精彩的部分吗 Jack?
And you know the best part, Jack?
是什么?
What?
你也在那儿
You're in this place.
我们在大洋航空815航班上相邻而坐
You know, we sat next to each other on Oceanic 815.
不曾坠毁
It never crashed.
我们互相交谈
We spoke to each other.
你看起来很高兴
You seemed happy.
或许我也有办法 把你带去那儿
You know, maybe I can find a way to bring you there, too.
Desmond 我尝试过一次
Desmond, I tried that once.
没有捷径 也无法重新来过
There are no shortcuts, no do-overs.
事情发生了就是发生了 相信我 我知道的
What happened, happened. Trust me, I know.
我们所做的很有意义
All of this matters.
要继续吗?
Shall we?
我们待这儿干嘛呀?
What are we doing here?
别人不让我告诉你
I'm not allowed to tell you.
什么叫"别人不让"啊?
What do you mean, you're "not allowed"?
要守规矩的 哥们
There are rules, dude.
谁定的规矩?
Whose rules?
不用担心 相信我就行了 没问题吧?
Don't worry about it. Just trust me, okay?
我相信你
I trust you.
我能问问 是什么让你这么相信我吗?
And what, may I ask, have I done to deserve your trust?
我觉得你是个好人 Sayid
I think you're a good guy, Sayid.
我知道 很多人说你是个坏人
I know a lot of people have told you that you're not.
可能你听多了
Maybe you've heard it so many times
也就信了
you started believing it.
但你不能让别人来告诉你 你是怎样的人 哥们
But you can't let other people tell you what you are, dude.
这得靠你自己来决定
You have to decide that for yourself.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你显然对我一无所知
You clearly don't know anything about me.
我知道你很多事情 哥们
I know a lot about you, dude.
看起来像是一顿暴打
Looks like a gnarly fight.
嘿 放开我弟弟!
Hey, leave my brother alone!
嘿 没事儿了
Hey, it's all right.
Sayid啊
Sayid.
Shannon啊
Shannon.
我刚挨了顿揍 哥们
I just got pounded, man.
谢谢你抽空来
Thanks for taking your sweet time.
很乐意为你效劳
It takes as long as it takes.
把她从澳大利亚带回来真让人讨厌
It was a pain in the ass getting her here from Australia.
没错 但是 哥们你知道么? 这很值哦
Yeah. But, dude? It was worth it.
我应该上去打个招呼吗?
Should I go get 'em?
别 让他们单独待一会儿吧
Nah. Let's give 'em a minute.
Linus 听得到吗?
Linus, are you there?
那是什么玩意儿?
What the hell's that?
Miles 你在哪儿?
Miles, where are you?
我们刚到九头蛇岛
We just got to Hydra Island.
- 我们正往飞机那儿赶  - Miles 听我说
- We're on our way to the plane.  - Miles, listen to me.
- 无论你做什么 都不要炸掉那架飞机!  - 我们不会炸掉它的
- Whatever you do, don't blow up that plane!  - We're not gonna blow it up.
我们要乘着它离开这个岛
We're gonna fly it the hell off the island.
- 快过来吧!  - 搞什么鬼啊?
- Just get over here now!  - What in the hell?
Claire啊
Claire.
Miles 我是Kate 你刚是说"Claire"吗?
Miles, it's Kate. Did you say "Claire"?
她还好吗?
Is she okay?
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
不要靠近!
Don't come any closer!
Miles啊
Miles?
Miles 发生什么事了?
Miles, what happened?
Miles 听得到吗?
Miles, are you there?
是他派你来杀我的 对吧?
He sent you to kill me, didn't he?
不是 我们跟Locke不是一伙的
No, listen. We're not with Locke.
我凭什么相信你?
Why should I believe you?
因为我们有机会可以离他远远的了
Because we have a real chance to get far, far away from him.
我们终于能摆脱他的魔爪了
We can be free of everything he ever did to us
再也不用回来了
and never look back.
我们可以回家了
We can go home.
要和我们一起走吗 Claire?
Will you come with us, Claire?
不
No.
好吧 我们...
All right, we...
我们轻轻地把他放下去
we lower him down nice and easy.
你知道一到下面就该做什么了吧?
You know what to do once you get down there?
知道
Aye.
我要去最亮的那束光那儿
I'll go where the light's brightest.
不要挂了哦
Don't get yourself killed.
这让你想起些什么了吧 Jack?
This remind you of anything, Jack?
什么?
What?
Desmond啊...
Desmond...
穿过下面那个洞
Going down into a hole in the ground.
如果那儿有个按钮
If there was a button down there to push,
我们再争论要不要去按
we could fight about whether or not to push it.
就像以前那样
It'd be just like old times.
你不是John Locke
You're not John Locke.
你套着他的皮囊 这是对他记忆的亵渎
You disrespect his memory by wearing his face,
你和他分明就是两个人
but you're nothing like him.
结果证明他都是对的
Turns out he was right about most everything.
我多么希望 我能在他活着的时候 告诉他这些啊
I just wish I could've told him that while he was still alive.
他的想法都是错的 Jack
He wasn't right about anything, Jack.
当这个岛
And when this island
沉到海底的时候 当你和岛一起沉下去的时候
drops into the ocean, and you drop with it,
那会儿你就会明白了
you're finally gonna realize that.
好吧 那就让我们看看 到底谁是对的吧
Well, we'll just have to see which one of us is right, then.
哦
Oh.
是医院打来的
It's the hospital.
去吧 我猜肯定是要紧事
Go ahead. I'm sure it's important.
- 对不起 我尽力赶回来  - 我知道 没事儿 去吧
- I am so sorry. I will be back as soon as I can.  - I know. It's cool. Go.
- 希望下次能更进一步互相了解 好么?  - 好的 一定
- We'll get to know each other better, I hope?  - Okay. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, for sure.
我 呃 我想就只剩我和你了吧 孩子
Well, I, uh, I guess it's just you and me, kid.
喂
Oy.
醒醒
Wake up.
醒醒 快啊 醒醒
Wake up. Come on. Wake up.
你在干嘛?
What are you doin'?
我只是根据指示办事
I'm just following the instructions.
你是乐队里的吧?
You're in the band, aren't you?
你怎么知道的?
How do you know that?
贝斯手 演出的时候叫醒我
我被一个肥仔打了一枪
I was shot by a fat man.
没事
It's all right.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
嘿 打扰一下 你知道乐队在哪儿吗?
Hey, excuse me. Do you know where the band is?
抱歉 呃 能再说一遍吗?
I'm sorry. Uh, pardon me?
我... 我想他是乐队里的吧
I... I think he's in the band.
是的 没错 当然了
Yes, yes. Of course.
他是"驱动轴"乐队的贝斯手
He's the bass player from Drive Shaft.
今晚他们为我伴奏
They're accompanying me tonight.
由我来弹钢琴
I play piano.
我叫Daniel 全名Daniel Widmore
I'm Daniel. Daniel Widmore.
我叫Charlotte
I'm Charlotte.
很高兴见到你 Charlotte
It's a great pleasure to meet you, Charlotte.
我也是
You, too.
请带路吧
Well, lead the way.
打扰一下 这是23号桌吗?
Excuse me. Is this Table 23?
是的 没错
Aye. Indeed it is.
Claire啊
Claire?
你们俩认识?
You two know each other?
女士们 先生们 晚上好
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
请朝这边看 可以吗?
May I have your attention, please?
欢迎参加这场为加州自然历史博物馆举办的
Welcome to this very special benefit concert
慈善音乐会
for the Golden State Natural History Museum.
我是Pierre Chang博士
I'm Dr. Pierre Chang.
谢谢
Thank you.
我想今晚对于我们来说意义非凡
I think we have quite a special evening ahead of us.
所以接下来我们直奔主题吧 好么?
So let's get to it, shall we?
我很荣幸
It is my pleasure
向大家介绍Daniel Widmore先生
to introduce you to Mr. Daniel Widmore,
以及"驱动轴"乐队
accompanied by Drive Shaft.
你还好吗?
You okay?
没事 没事 我只是... 要去下洗手间
Yeah. Yeah, I'm just... I'm just gonna use the bathroom.
我... 我去去就来
I'll... I'll be right back.
不!
No!
好像...
It looks like...
你搞错了
you were wrong.
再见了 Jack
Good-bye, Jack.
好像你也搞错了
Looks like you were wrong, too.
嗯 有人吗?
Um, hello?
有人吗?
Hello?
嗨 嗯 请问洗手间在哪? 啊! 噢!
Hi. Uh, do you know where the bathroom is? Mm! Ohh!
啊 可以去找医生来吗?
Uh, can you please get a doctor?
世界很小 对吧?
Small world, huh?
- 的确 你在这干嘛... 啊!  - 好了 噢! 好了 好了
Yeah, well, what are you doing... mm!  - Okay. Oh! Okay. Okay.
- 不要紧 过来 坐下  - 嗯 我... 我想他要出世了
- It's okay. Come on. Sit down.  - Um, I... I think he's coming.
我想我已经说得很清楚了
I thought I made it clear
你得阻止他
that you were to stop this.
的确非常清楚
Perfectly clear.
但我选择忽略你
I chose to ignore you.
一旦他们都知道了... 接下来怎么办?
And once they know... what then?
接下来?
Then?
我们走就是了
We're leaving.
你会带我儿子走吗?
Are you going to take my son?
不会的
Not with me.
不会
No.
呼吸就行 好吗? 呼吸 呼吸 深呼吸
Just breathe, okay? Just breathe, breathe, breathe.
- 医生马上就来了  - 嗯 不行!
- Help is on the way.  - Mnh-mnh!
- 已经... 来不及了 好像... 好像现在就要出来了  - 现在?
- It's hap... it's happening, like... like, right now.  - Right now?
嗯...
Um...
好吧 嗯... 我来帮你接生
Okay. Um... I'm gonna get you comfortable.
你得放松 并且深呼吸 可以吗?
I want you to relax and breathe, all right?
- 只要放松 并且深呼吸就好了  - 你是谁?
- Just relax and breathe.  - Who are you?
- 我是乐队的  - 啊!
- I'm with the band.  - Uhh!
- 听着 可以给我们拿点水和毯子吗?  - 水和毯子?
- Listen, can you get us some water and blankets, please?  - Water and blankets?
对 没错 呃...
Yeah. All right. Uh...
Claire啊...
Claire...
现在
This is about the time
你得用力生孩子了
when you're supposed to start pushing.
嗯... 嗯 不 我还没准备好 我... 我很害怕
Mnh... mnh. No, I'm not ready. I'm... I'm really scared.
我也很怕 知道吗? 非常怕
I'm scared, too, all right? Really scared.
但是我需要你用力 因为
Mm. But I'm gonna need you to push because
没你配合 我做不到 明白吗?
I can't do it without you. Okay?
来了
Okay.
一 二 三 用力!
One, two, three. Push!
很好 非常好 好 我们再来一次
Good. That's good. Okay, we're gonna try again.
你干得不错
You're doing good.
一 二 三 用力!
One, two, three. Push!
噢 噢... 好 用... 再用力
Oh. Uh... Okay. Push... push again.
用力啊!
Push!
噢!
Oh!
这是Aaron
It's Aaron.
这是...
It's...
我拿了一条毯子
I brought a blanket.
谢谢你
Thank you.
只是条毯子
It's just a blanket.
拿过去给她吧
Then go ahead and bring it to her.
我没找到水
Couldn't find any water.
Charlie啊
Charlie.
Claire啊?
Claire?
你好 Aaron
Hi, Aaron.
Aaron 嗨
Aaron. Hey.
现在明白了吗?
Do you understand?
接下来做什么?
So now what?
Hugo! 快走开!
Hugo! Get out of the way!
Desmond啊
Desmond!
我们会把你救出来的 好吗?
We're gonna get you out of here, all right?
这家伙真他妈重!
It's too damn heavy!
- 我们没办法把他弄出来!  - 无论如何得试试!
- There's no way we're gettin' it off of him!  - We have to try!
一... 二... 三!
One... Two... Three!
- 啊!  - 啊!
- Aah!  - Uhh!
怎么回事?!
What is happening?!
我来告诉你怎么回事! Locke说对了!
I'll tell you what's happening! Locke was right!
- 这个岛要沉了!  - Linus 回答!
- This island's goin' down!  - Linus, come in!
Linus 回答!
Linus, come in!
快回答!
Come in!
Miles 是你吗?
Miles, is that you?
是我 发生... 什么事了?
Yeah. What... what the hell is happening?
- Claire和你一起吗?  - 看到她了 但她不想跟我们来这
- Are you with claire?  - She's here, but she doesn't want to come with us.
你们在哪?
Come with you where?
Lapidus正在修理飞机
Lapidus is working on the plane right now.
修好了我们就起飞
Then we're taking off.
嗨 还要多久我们才能把它飞起来?
Hey, how much longer till we get this thing in the air?
我还得检查
I still have to check
水电情况!
the electrical and the hydraulics!
- 还要五小时 或者六小时  - 现在可能只有一小时了!
- Five hours, maybe six.  - You've got maybe one!
叫你们那帮人赶快过来! 我们一小时后起飞!
Get your asses over here! We're leaving in an hour!
去他的!
Son of a bitch!
- 我们要怎么到那去?!  - 我知道怎么去!
- How the hell are we supposed to get over there?!  - I know how we can get there!
Locke有一艘船!
Locke has a boat!
Locke啊
Locke!
我要你知道 Jack...
I want you to know, Jack...
你死得一钱不值
You died for nothing.
啊! 噢!
Aah! Uhh!
我为你留了一颗子弹!
I saved you a bullet!
你来晚了
You're too late.
干得好 Shepherd医生
Nice work, Dr. Shephard.
你脖子怎么了?
What happened to your neck?
该死的
Damn it.
好了 他现在稳定了 我得马上去洗个澡
Okay, he's stable. I'm gonna hop in the shower
看看我能不能在音乐会结束前 赶上David
and see if I can catch up with David before the concert's over.
有需要就打电话给我
So just give me a call if you need anything.
Shepherd医生? 他好像醒了
Dr. Shephard? He's waking up.
麻醉时我也在场
I watched the anesthesiologist.
给他注射的是最大剂量
He got the full dosage.
好吧
Okay.
这里交给我吧
I'll take it from here.
Locke先生?
Mr. Locke?
能听到我说话吗?
Can you hear me?
John 你醒了吗?
John, are you awake?
你刚刚进行了一场大手术
You just had major surgery,
所以你还不能动
so I need you to try not to move
放松就可以了 好吗?
and just relax, okay?
手术起作用了
It worked.
没错 进行得很顺利
Well, it went well.
但是 我们还不确定 你对手术的反应程度如何...
But we won't know how well you responded to the surgery for...
不是的 Shepherd医生 手术起作用了
No, Dr. Shephard. It worked.
我可以感觉到我的腿了
I can feel my legs.
John 这基本不可能
John, it's highly unlikely
你不可能这么快恢复知觉
that you would regain sensation that quickly.
所以 我们只要...
So let's just take it s...
噢
Ooh.
噢!
Oh!
噢
Ohh.
你看到了吗?
Did you see that?
看到什么?
See what?
你不记得了?
You don't remember?
嗯...
Um...
Locke先生
Mr. Locke,
请你 请你放松就好了
please, just, uh, just relax.
我们得... 我们得走了
What we need to do... what we need to do is go.
不 不 不 嘿 John
No, no, no. Hey, John.
- 你会跟我来吗?  - 我们哪都不会去
- Will you come with me?  - We're not going anywhere.
你刚刚才经历了一场大型脊椎手术...
You just had extensive spinal surgery...
而且我... 我得去找我儿子了
And I... I need to go see my son.
你没有儿子
You don't have a son.
你说什么?
What?
你没有儿子 Jack
You don't have a son, Jack.
医生?
Doctor?
Jane 嗯...
Jane, um...
你可以给Locke先生弄点什么 好让他静养吗?
Would you give Mr. Locke something to help him rest?
我得走了
I need to go.
Jack啊
Jack.
我希望有人能为你做
I hope that somebody does for you
你为我而做的事
what you just did for me.
噢 噢 我的天哪
Oh. Oh, my God.
噢!
Oh!
哦 Jack
Ohh. Jack.
我不会有事的
I'll be fine.
只要给我找些缝合线 这点伤就不碍事
Just find me some thread, and I can count to five.
嘿!
Hey!
噢 我的天!
Oh, my God!
发生什么事了?
What the hell happened?
Locke死了
Locke's dead.
结束了
It's over.
啊!
Uhh!
这真不像已经结束了
It sure don't feel like it's over.
打扰一下 Paik女士?
Excuse me. Ms. Paik?
有事吗?
Yes?
嗨
Hi.
我是洛杉矶警局的Ford探长
I'm Detective Ford. L.A.P.D.
很抱歉 听说您遭到了枪击
I'm sorry. I heard you were shot,
但是我希望您不要这么快出院
but I didn't expect you to be checking out so soon.
嘿
Hey.
你好... 探长
Hello... Detective.
我来是想确认下 你们有没有见过这个人
Well, I came by to check if you've seen this man.
他从看守所逃了 我们担心他会来找你们
He escaped custody, and we're worried he might come after you.
我会派一个警察来保护你们
I'm gonna assign a uniform to keep an eye on you
- 直到我们可以...  - 您没必要这么做
- until we can ap...  - You don't have to do that.
无意冒犯 这是我的职责 女士
All due respect, I have a job to do here, ma'am.
- 我得保证你们的安全  - 没事了 我已经安全了
- I need to keep you safe.  - It's okay. I am safe.
我们到那见
We'll see you there.
在哪见?
See me where?
好了
All right.
情况不妙 但应该能飞
It ain't pretty, but it's gonna work.
我得重启电路
I've gotta reset the electronics.
液压系统出了问题
Something's wrong with the hydraulics
就在前轮下端
down in the nose wheel.
你们俩谁懂机械吗? 嗯?
Is either one of you guys mechanical? Yeah?
我... 我曾给一个... 承包商装修过
I... I worked for a... a contractor renovating apartments
- 几年房子  - 这个 拿着...
- for a couple summers.  - Here, take that...
还有这个... 这个
And this... and this.
去下面 确保一切都正常
Go down there, make sure everything's hooked up right.
快去!
Go!
- Lapidus?  - 什么事?
- Lapidus?  - Yeah?
Frank 那边情况怎么样? 安排得如何?
Frank, how's it going over there? What's your timetable?
别烦我!
Don't bother me!
貌似他们有进展了
Sounds like they're making progress.
我们必须动身了
We gotta go now.
我不明白
I don't understand.
Locke已经死了 为什么还会这样?
Locke's dead. Why is this still happening?
因为不管Desmond关掉了什么
Because whatever Desmond turned off,
我都得再去把它打开
I need to turn it back on again.
但如果还是不行... 我没能把它修好...
But if it doesn't work... if I don't get it done...
你们现在就得离开 去搭上那架飞机
you all need to leave now. You need to be on that plane.
你可以跟我们一起走 Jack 你不必守在这里
You can come with us, too, Jack. You don't have to do this.
不 我必须履行的职责
No, I do have to do it.
不 没有必要
No, you don't.
让这个岛沉下去吧 Jack
Let this island sink, Jack.
Kate 我做不到
Kate, I can't.
- 划船过去 你觉得还能赶上吗?  - 是的 我想没问题
- You think you can get that boat across the channel in time?  - Yeah, I can manage.
祝你好运 James
Good luck to you, James.
谢谢你所做的一切 医生
Thanks, Doc, for everything.
James啊
James!
如果岛沉了 我同它一起沉下去
If the island's going down, I'm going down with it.
Hugo 你最好也走吧
Hugo. You better get going.
哦... 哦 没门 你认为我会走吗?
Unh... unh. No way. You think I'm going down that?
我跟你一起 老兄
I'm with you, dude.
好吧
Okay.
Kate啊...
Kate...
你赶紧走吧
You gotta go.
把Claire带上飞机
Get Claire on that plane.
告诉我 我们还会见面
Tell me I'm gonna see you again.
我爱你
I love you.
你能修好吗?
Can you fix it?
我会怀疑很多事情
I don't believe in a lot of things,
但我绝不怀疑管道胶带的性能
but I do believe in duct tape.
是的 我们能行
Yeah, I think we're good.
我们赶紧离开这鬼地方
Let's get the hell out of here.
唷 大胸男 这里是Sawyer和Kate
Yo, Chesty. It's Sawyer and Kate.
收到?
Yeah?
我们现在去坐帆船
We're on our way down to the sailboat,
然后再朝你们划去 别丢下我们!
then we're heading to you. Don't leave without us!
趁现在还可以起飞
We're gettin' off the ground
我们不能错失机会
while there's still ground to get off.
所以如果你们想走 最好赶紧过来
So if you wanna go, you better get your asses in gear.
Lapidus! Lapidus啊
Lapidus! Lapidus!
- 狗娘养的!  - 现在咋办?
- Son of a bitch!  - What now?
我们跳下去
We jump.
- 船上见了  - Kate!
- I'll see you at the boat.  - Kate!
嘿 你知道哪儿可以买点吃的吗?
Hey, you know where I can get some grub around here?
呃 自助餐厅已经关门了
Uh, the cafeteria's closed,
但是 走道尽头有个自动售货机
but there's a vending machine down the hallway.
谢谢 医生
Thanks, Doc.
嗯 别客气
Yeah, no problem.
噢 不会吧
Oh, come on.
真不可思议
Unbelievable.
需要我帮忙吗?
Can I help you?
没事 我是...
It's okay. I'm a...
我是警察
I'm a cop.
嗯 或许你应该瞧瞧机器的右边
Mm. Maybe you should read the machine its rights.
有意思
That's funny.
- 嗯 我可以告诉你个秘密吗?  - 请说
- Mm. Can I tell you a secret?  - Please.
如果你把插头拔了 然后再插上
If you unplug it, and then you plug it back in again,
糖就会掉下来
the candy just drops right down.
是吗?
Is that right?
是的 而且确切地说 这是合法的
Yes, and it's technically legal.
噢
Oh.
我来试试看
I'll give that a shot.
哎呀
Oops.
可行哦
It worked.
噢
Oh.
哇哦
Whoa.
你感觉到了吗?
Did you feel that?
- 改天我们应该去喝点咖啡  - 我很乐意
- We should get coffee sometime.  - I'd love to,
但是那个机器把我的钱吞了 我只剩一张票子了
but that machine ate my dollar. I only got one left.
我们可以各付各的
We could go Dutch.
Juliet啊
Juliet.
Juliet 是... 是我啊
Juliet, it's... it's me.
Juliet啊
Juliet.
是我 宝贝
It's me, baby.
我找到你了
I got you.
我找到你了 宝贝
I got you, baby.
是啊
Yeah.
吻我 James
Kiss me, James.
遵命 金发美女
You got it, blondie.
结束了
It's over.
什么?
Excuse me?
音乐会 结束了
Concert. It's over.
你在找人吗?
You are looking for someone?
嗯 今晚我本应该把儿子送到这里来 而...
Yeah. My son was supposed to bring him here tonight. And...
而我却没能来...
and I couldn't come...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
给点提示如何?
Where do I remember you from?
我偷了你的笔
I stole your pen.
什么?
What?
呃...
Um...
在大洋航空815航班上
Oceanic 815.
从悉尼飞来的
From Sydney.
在你走出洗手间时 我撞到了你
I bumped into you coming out of the bathroom,
然后... 我偷了你的笔
and... I stole your pen.
我是这样认识你的吗?
And that's how I know you?
不是
No.
你不是这样认识我的
That's not how you know me.
我想死你了
I missed you so much.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
我这是怎么了?
What is happening to me?
你是...
Who...
你是谁? 我并不...
Who are you? I don't...
我知道你还不理解 Jack
I know you don't understand, Jack.
但是 如果你跟来
But if you come with me,
你就会明白了
you will.
就在那边
It's over there.
我们怎么下去?
How we gettin' down there?
不是我们 是我一个人去
We're not. I'm going alone.
老兄 你不能独自一人下去 Desmond就是有去无回
Dude, you can't go down there alone. Desmond didn't make it.
你一个人怎么能逃出来?
How the hell are you gonna survive?
不行
No.
没门 我不会让你去送死
No way. I'm not gonna let you die.
Hurley 我已经是个死人了
Hurley, I'm already dead.
- 你说过你会保护这个岛的!  - 而这正是我要做的
- You said you'd protect the island!  - And that's what I'm doing.
- 你这是自杀!  - 不是的 命运这是不可避免的
- You're committing suicide!  - I'm not. This is the way it has to happen.
这就是我的职责
This is what I'm supposed to do.
你不该送死! 岛需要你!
You're not supposed to die! The island needs you!
Hurley啊...
Hurley...
它需要你
It needs you.
什么?
What?
它需要的是你 Hugo
It needs to be you, Hugo.
我不能
I can't.
应该是你
It's supposed to be you.
正因为是我 所以我才能这么做
It was only supposed to be me so I could do this.
但是 如果说它需要谁来爱护
But if someone has to take care of the island,
需要谁来保护的话 那么... 人选非你莫属
if someone has to protect it, then... then it should be you.
Hurley啊...
Hurley...
我相信你
I believe in you.
好的 我会保护它的
All right, I'll take it.
但是 只是暂时为之
But it's only temporary.
等你把光找回来回来 我就把你拉上来
As soon as you get that light back on, I'm pulling you up,
- 我就把这个权利还给你 怎么样?  - 成交
- And I'm giving it right back to you. Deal?  - Deal.
你有可以喝水的东西吗?
Do you have anything to drink?
随便什么用来装水的东西? 比如杯子... 或者水壶
Anything to drink out of? A... a cup. A canteen.
我有
I do.
这个行吗?
Is that okay?
完美
Perfect.
把这喝了
Drink this.
这样就行了?
Is that it?
现在你跟我一样
Now you're like me.
第二次希望有效
Second time's a charm.
最好这样 因为我们肯定
It better be, 'cause we sure as hell
没有电量启动第三次
don't have the battery power for a third time.
可以了吗?
Is that good?
朋友 那可是天簌之音
That, my friends, is pure music.
慢点
Easy.
慢点 慢点
Easy. Easy.
老兄!
Dude!
Desmond啊
Desmond!
能听见我说话吗?
Can you hear me?
啊! 啊!
Aah! Ah!
光...
The light...
我把它灭了
I put it out.
还是没用
It didn't work.
我以为我已经离开这儿了
I thought I'd leave this place.
我来扶你 来吧
I got you. Come on.
来吧 啊!
Come on. Ah!
可我还在这儿
I'm still here.
你是对的 Jack
You were right, Jack.
对啊 什么都有第一次嘛
Yeah, well, there's a first time for everything.
啊!
Aah!
啊! 我必须要把石头塞回去
Uhh! I have to put it back.
- 它像个下水道一样  - 你刚才那么做了?
- It was like a drain.  - That's what you did?
- 你把石头从洞里拔出来了?  - Jack 你不行 听我说
- You took that stone out of that hole over there?  - Jack, you can't. Listen.
即使你把它放回去了 你的小命也就跟着玩完了 这件事必须我来干
Even if you turn it back on, it'll kill ya. It has to be me.
Desmond 你做得够多了
Desmond, you've done enough.
你想做事情啊? 那就回家跟你老婆孩子团聚
You wanna do something? Go home and be with your wife and son.
那你怎么办 Jack?
How about you, Jack?
兄弟 我们来生再见
I'll see you in another life, brother.
Claire啊
Claire?
哦 糟糕
Oh, that ain't good.
Miles 看着舱门外! 你当我的眼睛
Miles, go look out the door! You're gonna be my eyes while I
帮我倒飞机 Richard 替他传话给我
back this out of here. Richard, go tell me what he says.
Claire啊
Claire!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
来吧! 我们得走了! 快来!
Come on! We gotta go! Come on!
- Claire 快走 求你了  - 我不能!
- Claire, come on, please.  - I can't!
- 为什么?!  - 看看我现在!
- Why?!  - Look at me!
这座岛把我逼疯了
This island's made me crazy.
我... 我不想让Araon看到我这个样子
I... I don't want Aaron to see me like this.
我都... 我都不知道该怎么样当妈了
I don't... I don't even know how to be a mother anymore.
听我说 我们谁都不会当母亲
Listen to me. None of us do.
谁都不是与生俱来
Not at first.
但你不会是一个人
But you're not alone.
让我帮你
Let me help you.
来吧
Now come on.
走吧
Let's go.
- 后面有地儿吗?!  - Miles 后面有地儿吗?
- Are we clear?!  - Miles, are we clear?
- 嗯 我觉得足够了!  - 他说可以
- Yeah, it looks like it to me!  - He says we're good.
你最好祈祷我们没事 小Ricky
You better prey we are, Ricky boy,
因为我要让飞机调个头 抓住了!
'cause I'm gonna spin her around. Hold on!
- Sawyer! 让他停下! 告诉他我们来了!  - Lapidus! Lapidus!
- Sawyer! Tell him to stop! Tell him we're coming!  - Lapidus! Lapidus!
Lapidus 等等!
Lapidus, hold on!
好了 我们可以走了!
All right, we're good to go!
我们走吧!
Let's go!
见鬼?
What the hell?
伙计们 有几个迟到的 开门去
Boys, we got some late arrivals. Open the door.
快点!
Come on!
啊!
Uhh!
不
No.
不要
别这样
No.
我们没时间了!
We're running out of time!
- Jim 总是在最后一秒见到你  - 我也很高兴见到你 Enos
- Way to wait till the last second, Jim.  - Good to see you, too, Enos.
他们上来了!
We got 'em!
各位 系紧安全带!
Everybody, buckle up tight!
抓住了!
Hold on!
Frank 我们上路吧
Here we go, Frank.
拜托
Come on.
起飞吧
上帝保佑
Amen.
他成功了 光又回来了
He did it. The light's back on.
哥们儿 拉
Dude, pull.
坚持住 Jack!
Hang on, Jack!
拉上来了!
Got him!
Desmond啊
Desmond?
不是吧
No.
Jack啊
Jack!
你好 Benjamin
Hello, Benjamin.
你好 John
Hello, John.
大家都在里面吗?
Is everyone already inside?
是的 大多数都在
I believe most of them are, yes.
嗯
Mm.
很抱歉 我曾那样对你 John
I'm very sorry for what I did to you, John.
我很自私
I was selfish
很嫉妒你
and jealous.
我想得到你所拥有的一切
I wanted everything you had.
我有什么?
What did I have?
你很特殊 John
You were special, John.
而我很平凡
And I wasn't.
呃 Ben 如果有用的话
Well, if it helps, Ben,
我原谅你
I forgive you.
谢谢你 John
Thank you, John.
那确实很有帮助
That does help.
是言语所无法表达的
It matters more than I can say.
那你现在要做什么?
What are you gonna do now?
我还有些事情要处理
I have some things that I still need to work out.
我可能会再待一会儿
I think I'll stay here a while.
你知道吗 我觉得你不用再待在轮椅里了
You know, I don't think you need to be in that chair anymore.
Ben 再见
Good-bye, Ben.
Desmond会好起来的
I think Desmond's gonna be okay.
Jack... 走了
Jack's... gone.
对吗?
Isn't he?
这是他的职责 Hugo
He did his job, Hugo.
现在是我的职责了
It's my job now.
我到底应该做什么?
What the hell am I supposed to do?
我觉得你要做你擅长的
I think you do what you do best.
照顾大伙儿
Take care of people.
你可以从帮助Desmond回家开始
You can start by helping Desmond get home.
但要怎么做?
But how?
人们不能离开这座岛
People can't leave the island.
那是Jacob规定的
That's how Jacob ran things.
也许有别的方法
Maybe there's another way.
一个更好的方法
A better way.
你会帮我吗?
Will you help me?
你说什么?
I'm sorry?
我可以招一些人 比如... 有经验的人
I could really use someone with, like... experience
就一段时间
for a little while.
Ben 你会帮我吗?
Will you help me, Ben?
荣幸之至
I'd be honored.
太棒了
Cool.
哦! 嘿 哥们儿
Oh! Hey, dude.
你好 Hugo
Hello, Hugo.
我们都在里面
We're all inside.
我不想进去
I don't think I'm coming in.
你知道...
You know...
你是个很好的二把手
you were a real good Number Two.
你也是个很出色的一把手 Hugo
And you were a great Number One, Hugo.
谢谢 哥们儿
Thanks, dude.
一会儿见
I'll see you.
你知道我们在哪儿吗?
Do you know where we are?
这是应该为我父亲举办葬礼的地方
This is where I was gonna have my father's funeral.
他死在了澳大利亚
He died in Australia.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
为什么带我来这?
Why did you bring me here?
因为这里将是
Because this is where
为你父亲举办葬礼的地方
you are gonna have your father's funeral.
你可以在后面逛逛
You can go in around back.
等等 你... 你去哪?
Wait. W... where are you going?
里面
Inside.
我在那等你...
I'll be waiting for you there...
等你准备好
once you're ready.
准备好什么?
Ready for what?
离开
To leave.
嘿 孩子
Hey, kiddo.
爸爸?
Dad?
你好 Jack
Hello, Jack.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你死了
You died.
对
Yeah.
是的 我死了
Yes, I did.
那你怎么又在这儿?
Then how are you here right now?
那你怎么在这儿?
How are you here?
我也死了
I died, too.
没事儿的
It's okay.
没事儿
没关系的 儿子
It's okay, son.
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, dad.
我也爱你 儿子
I love you, too, son.
你...
Are you...
你是真的吗?
Are you real?
希望是
I sure hope so.
是的 我是真的
Yeah, I'm real.
你是真的
You're real.
你发生过的每一件事都是真的
Everything that's ever happened to you is real.
在教堂里面的所有人...
All those people in the church...
也都是真的
they're all real, too.
他们都...
They're all...
他们都死了?
they're all dead?
每个人都会死 孩子
Everyone dies sometime, kiddo.
有些人死在你前面 有些...
Some of them before you, some...
死在你后面
long after you.
但他们怎么现在都在?
But why are they all here now?
呃 在这里没有"现在"
Well, there is no "now" here.
我们在哪儿 爸爸?
Where are we, dad?
这是个... 你们能聚在一起的地方
This is a place that you... that you all made together
这样 你能找到其他人
so that you could find one another.
你生命中最重要的一段日子
The most important part of your life
就是和他们共同度过的时光
was the time that you spent with these people.
这就是为什么你们都在这里
That's why all of you are here.
Jack 没有人能独自度过这段时光
Nobody does it alone, Jack.
你需要他们每一个人
You needed all of them,
同样 他们也需要你
and they needed you.
需要我干什么?
For what?
怀念
To remember.
还有... 放手
And to... let go.
Kate啊...
Kate...
她说我们要离开
she said we were leaving.
不是离开 不是
Not leave. No.
是继续生活
Moving on.
我们要去哪儿?
Where are we going?
让我们去找找看吧
Let's go find out.
我们都在等你呢
We've been waitin' for ya.
迷失 全剧终 谢谢观赏